

ETHICAL HACKER - DEVELOPER

# MANUEL BARREIRO

#### **CONTACT**

Mobile: +598 092 447 494 Email: manuu307@gmail.com Linkedin: Manuel Barreiro

GitHub: https://github.com/manuu307

Site: https://my-portfolio-2zzsydf6aq-uc.a.run.app

#### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

I am a proactive person and an excellent problem solver. I like to be aware of the new trends related to the world of technology and constantly improving my knowledge. I consider myself to have good interpersonal skills which allow me to have excellent relationships in the work environment.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Technical service - independent (2012 - 2020):

- -> PC Maintenance and Repair.
  - Repair, Maintenance and Assembly of PC's (Hardware and Software)
  - Repair Notebooks (Software)

#### Freelance developer (2019 - 2021):

-> Web development.

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, WordPress

#### Hacknoid (April 2021 - Today):

- -> Cibersecurity and Python development.
  - Development of scripts for automation.
  - Cybersecurity in Pentester and Ethical Hacker modality.
  - OT Security: Vulnerability analysis in ICS/SCADA devices.

#### **OTHER SKILLS**

- · Fast learning.
- Good communication.
- Organized.
- Creative.
- · Proactive.
- Autodidactic.

#### **EXPERTISE**

#### Development:

- Frontend: HTML, CSS, JavaScript (ReactJs and VueJs).
- WordPress.
- Mobile: React Native.
- Backend: NodeJs, TypeScript, PHP, Python, SQL y NoSQL.

#### Sistems and Infrastructure:

- Admin. Linux and Windows sistems.
- Cloud services GCP, AWS, Azure.
- Operational tecnology (ICS/SCADA)

# Networking and Cybersecurity:

- Recognition phase.
- Port scanning and system identification.
- Vulnerability scan.
- Exploitation of vulnerabilities.
- Assessment of risks found.

## Mercurio Data Science (April 2021 - Today):

- -> Full-Stack Developer Data scraping and analysis
  - VueJs.
  - · NodeJs.
  - TypeScript.
  - Python.
  - ReactJs
  - MySQL.

# Bug Bounty - independant (2020 - 2021):

- -> Bug Bounty Programs (Microsoft Azure Y Google Cloud).
  - · Bug hunting in web applications.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### SCHOOL:

- SCHOOL AND HIGH SCHOOL SAN JOSE DE LA PROVIDENCIA.
- BACCALAUREATE: COMPUTER TECHNOLOGICAL INSTITUTE (I.T.I).

#### **COURSES:**

- CYBERSECURITY BIOS
- FUNDAMENTALS OF OT CYBERSECURITY UDEMY
- HACKTHEBOX ACADEMY AND TRYHACKME
- HUNDREDS OF DEVELOPMENT COURSES/TUTORIALS

#### LANGUAJES:

ADVANCED ENGLISH - ACCESS INSTITUTE

#### **ABOUT ME**

I consider myself passionate about technology from the moment I got my first PC at 8 years old. Before entering U.T.U as a computer science student, I was already creating online game servers, simple web pages in WordPress, Blogs and I was completely familiar with the hardware. Currently I divide my time into 50% ethical hacking and 50% programming, which I think complement each other perfectly. My ambitions for the future are to continue perfecting myself and gradually add artificial intelligence to my expertise combo. Now a days i use A.I in order to improve productivity and better code writing.